http://www.satimagingcorp.com/about/privacy-policy/

ContactAOIGoogle EarthOrderTechnical Contact FormSpanish Contact FormDeutschFrancaisItalianoSatellitesWorldView-4 (0.31m)WorldView-3 (0.31m)WorldView-2 (0.46m)WorldView-1 (0.46m)GeoEye-1 (0.46m)Pleiades-1A (0.5m)Pleiades-1B (0.5m)SuperView-1 (0.5m)KOMPSAT-3A (0.55m)KOMPSAT-3 (0.7m)QuickBird (0.65m)Gaofen-2 (0.8m)TripleSat (0.8m)IKONOS (0.82m)IKONOS Stereo ImagerySkySat-1 (0.8m)SkySat-2 (0.8m)Jilin-1 (1m)Jilin-1 Optical SatelliteJilin-1 Smart Video SatelliteJilin-1 Hyperspectral SatelliteTerraSAR-XSPOT-6 (1.5m)SPOT-7 (1.5m)Other Satellites (2m-20m)FORMOSAT-2 (2m)TH-01 (2m)ALOS (2.5m)CARTOSAT-1 (2.5m)SPOT-5 (2.5m-5m)Dove (3m)RapidEye (5m)Sentinel-2A (10m)LANDSAT 7 ETM+ (15m)LANDSAT 8 (15m)ASTER (15m)CBERS-2 (20m)GalleryWorldView-4WorldView-3WorldView-2WorldView-1GeoEye-1Pleiades-1APleiades-1BKOMPSAT-3QuickBirdIKONOSSkySat-1TripleSatTerraSAR-XSPOT-6SPOT-7TH-01RapidEyeLANDSAT 7 ETM+LANDSAT 8High ResolutionMedium Resolution3D Terrain Flythroughs3D Terrain ModellingGeographic Information Systems (GIS)Historical SitesMore ImageryALOSCARTOSAT-1SPOT-5DoveSentinel-2AASTERCBERS-2FORMOSAT-2Aerial PhotosApplicationsEnergyMiningOil and GasOil and Gas DevelopmentOil and Gas ExplorationOil and Gas ProductionPipeline and TransmissionEngineering and Construction3D Urban and Terrain ModelingAirport Mapping DatabaseCadastre and Land RecordsUrban and Land DevelopmentDefense and SecurityCrime MappingHomeland SecurityEnvironmental ManagementGlobal Climate ChangeUrban PlanningConservationArchaeologyCoastal ManagementHabitat MappingWildlife MonitoringLand Cover and Change DetectionNatural DisastersHurricanesNatural HazardsLandslidesMedia and EntertainmentNatural ResourcesAgriculture MappingAgriculturaVegetation Index MapsIndice De Vegetacion VerdeGVI Sample ImagesAgricultura MapasSoil Zone IndexIndoce de la Cubierta VegetalTreeGrading MapsTreeGrading de AgriculturaForestryControl Remoto de SilviculturaSoil Moisture and Ocean SalinityTourismServices3D Terrain ModellingATCORAtmospheric CompensationConsultancy3D Digital Elevation ModelFeature ExtractionGeographic Information SystemsImage ProcessingOrthorectificationResourcesGeospatial TechnologyRemote SensingAboutPressPressContact UsPress Contact Us Satellite Imaging CorporationContactAOIGoogle EarthOrderTechnical Contact FormSpanish Contact FormDeutschFrancaisItalianoSatellitesWorldView-4 (0.31m)WorldView-3 (0.31m)WorldView-2 (0.46m)WorldView-1 (0.46m)GeoEye-1 (0.46m)Pleiades-1A (0.5m)Pleiades-1B (0.5m)SuperView-1 (0.5m)KOMPSAT-3A (0.55m)KOMPSAT-3 (0.7m)QuickBird (0.65m)Gaofen-2 (0.8m)TripleSat (0.8m)IKONOS (0.82m)IKONOS Stereo ImagerySkySat-1 (0.8m)SkySat-2 (0.8m)Jilin-1 (1m)Jilin-1 Optical SatelliteJilin-1 Smart Video SatelliteJilin-1 Hyperspectral SatelliteTerraSAR-XSPOT-6 (1.5m)SPOT-7 (1.5m)Other Satellites (2m-20m)FORMOSAT-2 (2m)TH-01 (2m)ALOS (2.5m)CARTOSAT-1 (2.5m)SPOT-5 (2.5m-5m)Dove (3m)RapidEye (5m)Sentinel-2A (10m)LANDSAT 7 ETM+ (15m)LANDSAT 8 (15m)ASTER (15m)CBERS-2 (20m)GalleryWorldView-4WorldView-3WorldView-2WorldView-1GeoEye-1Pleiades-1APleiades-1BKOMPSAT-3QuickBirdIKONOSSkySat-1TripleSatTerraSAR-XSPOT-6SPOT-7TH-01RapidEyeLANDSAT 7 ETM+LANDSAT 8High ResolutionMedium Resolution3D Terrain Flythroughs3D Terrain ModellingGeographic Information Systems (GIS)Historical SitesMore ImageryALOSCARTOSAT-1SPOT-5DoveSentinel-2AASTERCBERS-2FORMOSAT-2Aerial PhotosApplicationsEnergyMiningOil and GasOil and Gas DevelopmentOil and Gas ExplorationOil and Gas ProductionPipeline and TransmissionEngineering and Construction3D Urban and Terrain ModelingAirport Mapping DatabaseCadastre and Land RecordsUrban and Land DevelopmentDefense and SecurityCrime MappingHomeland SecurityEnvironmental ManagementGlobal Climate ChangeUrban PlanningConservationArchaeologyCoastal ManagementHabitat MappingWildlife MonitoringLand Cover and Change DetectionNatural DisastersHurricanesNatural HazardsLandslidesMedia and EntertainmentNatural ResourcesAgriculture MappingAgriculturaVegetation Index MapsIndice De Vegetacion VerdeGVI Sample ImagesAgricultura MapasSoil Zone IndexIndoce de la Cubierta VegetalTreeGrading MapsTreeGrading de AgriculturaForestryControl Remoto de SilviculturaSoil Moisture and Ocean SalinityTourismServices3D Terrain ModellingATCORAtmospheric CompensationConsultancy3D Digital Elevation ModelFeature ExtractionGeographic Information SystemsImage ProcessingOrthorectificationResourcesGeospatial TechnologyRemote SensingAboutPressSearchPrivacy PolicyDiscover what's possible. Get a complimentary consultation today.Contact Us NowHomeAboutThank you for placing your trust in Satellite Imaging Corporation. We are committed to protecting your personal data.This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their Personally Identifiable Information (PII) is being used online. PII is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context.Please read our privacy policy carefully to understand how we collect, use, and handle your Personally Identifiable Information.Information We CollectWhen inquiring about our services or registering on our site, you may be asked to enter your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, or other details that are necessary to conduct business or provide a personalized experience.We collect personal information from you when you use our contact form to inquire about our services, register a personal account, place an order, or subscribe to a newsletter.Usage of Personal InformationYour personal information is used to:
• Personalize your experience by delivering content and product information that we believe will interest you. • Contact you and follow up on project inquiries. • Send periodic e-mails regarding your account, order(s), or other products and services.Handling of Sensitive InformationOur website is scanned on a regular basis for known security vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible.Your personal information may only be accessed by a limited number of people with special access rights to our corporate systems, and are required to keep any personal information confidential.Any credit card transactions are processed using a secure gateway. No credit card information is stored on or passed through our web servers.Cookies and Cookie Opt-OutCookies contain small amounts of data that may persist between site visits and allow us to identify a unique web browser. We use cookies to personalize your experience, provide login capabilities, and conduct anonymous web analytics. In addition, our third-party ad partners use cookies to serve online advertisements to you and other visitors.You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. Please refer to the documentation provided with your web browser for further instructions about how to manage and disable cookies. Because certain site features depend upon cookies, disabling them may result in a degraded experience.Third-Party LinksWe may occasionally link to resources that are hosted on external websites. Satellite Imaging Corporation has no control over the privacy policies or practices of these other sites, and is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of web sites to which we link, list, rank, or identify by means of a search.Satellite Imaging Corporation takes no responsibility for the products, services, policies or actions of third parties or the content of third party web sites. We encourage you to be aware when you are leaving our site and to read the privacy policies of each web site you visit.Third-Party DisclosureWe do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information unless we provide you with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety.At our discretion, non-personally identifying visitor information may be provided to third parties for marketing, advertising, or other purposes.GoogleWe use Google Analytics to conduct anonymous web analytics. Please refer to the Google Analytics privacy policy for more information.AdRollOur display advertising partner, AdRoll, enables us to present you with retargeting advertising on other sites based on your previous interaction with Satellite Imaging Corporation. The techniques our partners employ do not collect personal information, such as your name, e-mail address, postal address, or telephone number. You can visit this page to opt out of AdRoll’s and their partners’ targeted advertising.Do Not TrackWe do not currently acknowledge or take action based on Do Not Track headers.Children and COPPAWe do not knowingly collect any information from children under 13 years of age.Data Breach NotificationsShould we become aware of a data breach, we will make reasonable efforts to notify affected users via e-mail within 7 business days. In addition, we will post a notification on our site.E-Mail Opt-OutWe use your e-mail address to:Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questionsProcess orders and to send information and updates pertaining to ordersProvide additional information related to your product and/or serviceMarket to our mailing list subscribersStay in contact with our clients following their original transactions with usIf you would like to remove yourself from our mailing list, please e-mail us at info@satimagingcorp.com, and we will promptly remove you.Contact InformationIf you have concerns or questions about our privacy policy, or would like to correct or access any of your personal information, please use the following information to contact us.Satellite Imaging Corporation Email: info@satimagingcorp.com Phone: (832) 237-2900 x203ChangesAt our discretion, we may periodically update this privacy policy. When an update occurs, a revision notice will be posted on this page.Last Revised:July 18, 2015Satellite Imaging Corporation is an official Value Added Reseller (VAR) of imaging and geospatial data products for:
ContactSatellitesGalleryApplicationsServicesAboutTerms of UsePrivacy PolicySite MapCopyright © 2001-2017 Satellite Imaging Corporation. All rights reserved.Facebook Twitter LinkedIn
